Products[Domains  
Domains are like the phone book of the internet. Each website, email server, and digital service has an IP (Internet Protocol) address assigned to it. Because it's difficult for visitors to remember these numerical IP addresses, domain names like "yourname.xyz" were created and can since be registered.](https://gentlent.com/domains)[Dynamic DNS  
Dynamic DNS allows you to access your home network from anywhere in the world. We connect a subdomain to your synced home IP.](https://gentlent.com/dynamic-dns)[IP Resources  
Gentlent provides IP address space and Autonomous System Numbers (ASNs) for organizations and individuals in the RIPE region, enabling you to establish your own network, improve routing, and enhance internet performance and reliability](https://gentlent.com/ip-resources)[Gentlent SafeSurf  
SafeSurf shows you security indicators in the omnibar for post-EV safer surfing.](https://gentlent.com/safesurf)[Coming soon  
Coming soon](https://gentlent.com/)

[Contact  
Gentlent's global support is free of charge for all our customers.](https://gentlent.com/contact)

Data protection declaration
===========================

Last updated on July 14, 2023.

Unless stated otherwise below, the provision of your personal data is neither legally nor contractually obligatory, nor required for conclusion of a contract. You are not obliged to provide your data. Not providing it will have no consequences. This only applies as long as the processing procedures below do not state otherwise.

“Personal data” is any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.

### Server log files

You can use our websites without submitting personal data.

Every time our website is accessed, user data is transferred to us or our web hosts/IT service providers by your internet browser and stored in server log files. This stored data includes for example the name of the site called up, date and time of the request, the IP address, amount of data transferred and the provider making the request. The processing is carried out on the basis of Article 6(1) f) GDPR due to our legitimate interests in ensuring the smooth operation of our website as well as improving our services.

Contact
-------

### Responsible person

Contact us at any time. The person responsible for data processing is:

Tom Klein  
Am Trippelsberg 92  
40589 Düsseldorf  
Germany  
Tel: [+49 (0) 211 86843 - 0](tel:+490211868430)  
Email: [support@gentlent.com](mailto:support@gentlent.com)

### Proactive contact of the customer by e-mail

If you make contact with us proactively via email, we shall collect your personal data (name, email address, message text) only to the extent provided by you. The purpose of the data processing is to handle and respond to your contact request.

If the initial contact serves to implement pre-contractual measures (e.g. consultation in the case of purchase interest, order creation) or concerns an agreement already concluded between you and us, this data processing takes place on the basis of Article 6(1)(b) GDPR.

If the initial contact occurs for other reasons, this data processing takes place on the basis of Article 6(1)(f) GDPR for the purposes of our overriding, legitimate interest in handling and responding to your request. **In this case, on grounds relating to your particular situation, you have the right to object at any time to this processing of personal data concerning you and carried out on the basis of Article 6(1)(f) GDPR.**

We will only use your email address to process your request. Your data will subsequently be deleted in compliance with statutory retention periods, unless you have agreed to further processing and use.

### Collection and processing when using the contact form

When you use the contact form we will only collect your personal data (name, email address, message text) in the scope provided by you. The data processing is for the purpose of making contact.

If the initial contact serves to implement pre-contractual measures (e.g. consultation in the case of purchase interest, order creation) or concerns an agreement already concluded between you and us, this data processing takes place on the basis of Article 6(1)(b) GDPR.

If the initial contact occurs for other reasons, this data processing takes place on the basis of Article 6(1)(f) GDPR for the purposes of our overriding, legitimate interest in handling and responding to your request. **In this case, on grounds relating to your particular situation, you have the right to object at any time to this processing of personal data concerning you and carried out on the basis of Article 6(1)(f) GDPR.**

We will only use your email address to process your request. Finally your data will be deleted, unless you have agreed to further processing and use.

### Collection and processing in case of applications via e-mail

In case of interest, website visitors may apply to vacancies advertised on our website by e-mail. We only collect your personal data to the extent provided by you. This includes your contact details (e.g., name, e-mail address, telephone number), details of your professional qualifications and training, details of further professional training and performance-specific evidence.

The purpose of this data processing is to contact you and to decide on the establishment of an employment relationship with you. The provision of the data is necessary to carry out the application procedure. The processing of your personal data takes place on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1(b) GDPR in conjunction with Art. 26 para. 1 Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG) for the implementation of pre-contractual measures (undergoing the application procedure as an initiation of the employment contract).

If you have given us permission for the processing of personal data for the inclusion in our pool of applicants, e.g., by checking a checkbox, the processing takes place on the basis of Art. 6 par. 1(a) GDPR. You can revoke your consent at any time without affecting the legality of the processing carried out on the basis of your consent until the revocation.

If specific categories of personal data within the meaning of Art. 9 para. 1 of the GDPR are requested from the applicants, such as information on the degree of severe disability, this is carried out on the basis of Art. 9 para. 2(b) GDPR, so that we can exercise the rights arising from labor law and the social security and social protection legislation and fulfill our obligations in this regard.

We will store your personal data as long as this is necessary for the decision about your application. Your data will then be deleted after six months at the latest, provided that you have not consented to further processing and use. If an employment relationship is established following the application procedure, the data provided will be further processed and then transferred to the personnel file for the purposes of implementing the employment relationship pursuant to Art. 6 para. 1 (b) GDPR in conjunction with Art. 26 Para. 1 of the Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG).

### Collection and processing when using the application form

When using the application form, we collect your personal data only to the extent provided by you. This includes your contact details (e.g., name, e-mail address, telephone number), details of your professional qualifications and training, details of further professional training and performance-specific evidence.

The purpose of this data processing is to contact you and to decide on the establishment of an employment relationship with you. The provision of the data is necessary to carry out the application procedure. The processing of your personal data takes place on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1(b) GDPR in conjunction with Art. 26 para. 1 Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG) for the implementation of pre-contractual measures (undergoing the application procedure as an initiation of the employment contract).

If you have given us permission to process personal data for inclusion in our pool of applicants, e.g., by checking a checkbox, the processing takes place on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1(a) GDPR. You can revoke your consent at any time without affecting the legality of the processing carried out on the basis of your consent until the revocation.

If specific categories of personal data within the meaning of Art. 9 para. 1 of the GDPR are requested from the applicants, such as information on the degree of severe disability, this is carried out on the basis of Art. 9 para. 2(b) GDPR, so that we can exercise the rights arising from labor law and the social security and social protection legislation and fulfill our obligations in this regard.

We will store your personal data as long as this is necessary for the decision about your application. Your data will then be deleted after six months at the latest, provided that you have not consented to further processing and use. If an employment relationship is established following the application procedure, the data provided will be further processed and then transferred to the personnel file for the purposes of implementing the employment relationship pursuant to Art. 6 para. 1 (b) GDPR in conjunction with Art. 26 Para. 1 of the Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG).

### Collection and processing when sending images via upload

We provide an upload function for image files on our website. It is thus possible to send images to us by means of encrypted data transmission. With the transmission of your images, we may collect your personal data (image of an identifiable person) only to the extent provided by you. The purpose of data processing is to create personalized products. The sent image serves as a template for the product and is used for this purpose (e.g., T-shirt print). The processing is carried out on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1(b) GDPR and is required for the performance of a contract with you. Your data will not be transferred.

We only use the image you send within the scope of service provision. Your data will then be deleted subject to legal retention periods, provided that you have not consented to further processing and use.

### Collection and processing when images are sent by e-mail

You have the option to send us images via e-mail in connection with the order of a personalized product.

With the transmission of your images, we may collect your personal data (image of an identifiable person) only to the extent provided by you. The purpose of data processing is to create personalized products. The sent image serves as a template for the product and is used for this purpose (e.g. T-shirt print). The processing is carried out on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1(b) GDPR and is required for the completion of a contract with you.

Your data will not be transferred.

We only use the image you send within the scope of service provision. Your data will then be deleted subject to legal retention periods, provided that you have not consented to further processing and use.

Customer account / Orders
-------------------------

### Customer account

When you open a customer account, we will collect your personal data in the scope given there. The data processing is for the purpose of improving your shopping experience and simplifying order processing. The processing will be carried out on the basis of art. 6 (1) lit. a GDPR with your consent. You can withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us without affecting the legality of the processing carried out with your consent up to the withdrawal. Your customer account will then be deleted.

### Collection, processing, and transfer of personal data in orders

When you submit an order we only collect and use your personal data insofar as this is necessary for the fulfilment and handling of your order as well as processing of your queries. The provision of data is necessary for conclusion of a contract. Failure to provide it will prevent the conclusion of any contract. The processing will occur on the basis of Article 6(1) b) GDPR and is required for the fulfilment of a contract with you.

Your data is transferred here for example to the shipping companies and dropshipping providers, payment service providers, service providers for handling the order and IT service providers that you have selected. We will comply strictly with legal requirements in every case. The scope of data transmission is restricted to a minimum.

Evaluations / Advertising
-------------------------

### Data collection when you post a comment

When you comment on an article or a contribution, we collect your personal data (name, email address, comment text) only in the scope provided by you. The processing serves to allow you to comment and to display comments. By submitting the comment you agree to the processing of the transmitted data. The processing will be carried out on the basis of art. 6 (1) lit. a GDPR with your consent. You can withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us without affecting the legality of the processing carried out with your consent up to the withdrawal. You personal data will then be deleted.

On publication of your comment only the name you have entered will be published.

On submission of your comment your IP address will also be saved in order to prevent misuse of the comment function and to ensure the security of our IT systems. By submitting the comment you agree to the processing of the transmitted data. The processing will be carried out on the basis of art. 6 (1) lit. a GDPR with your consent. You can withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us without affecting the legality of the processing carried out with your consent up to the withdrawal. Your IP address will then be deleted.

### Use of your email address for mailing of newsletters

We use your email address outside of contractual processing exclusively to send you a newsletter for our own marketing purposes, if you have explicitly agreed to this. The processing will be carried out on the basis of art. 6 (1) lit. a GDPR with your consent. You can withdraw your consent at any time without affecting the legality of the processing carried out with your consent up to the withdrawal. You can unsubscribe from the newsletter at any time using the relevant link in the newsletter or by contacting us. Your email address will then be removed from the distributor.

Payment service providers
-------------------------

### Use of PayPal

On our website we use the PayPal payment service of PayPal (Europe) S.à.r.l. et Cie, S.C.A. (22-24 Boulevard Royal L-2449, Luxembourg; "PayPal"). The data processing serves the purpose of offering you payment via the payment service. By selecting and using payment via PayPal, the data required for processing the payment will be transmitted to PayPal in order to enable us to fulfil the contract with you with the selected payment method. This processing is carried out on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b GDPR.

All PayPal transactions are subject to PayPal Privacy Policy. You can find these at [https://www.paypal.com/de/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/de/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full).

### Use of PayPal Plus

On our website we use the PayPal Plus payment service of PayPal (Europe) S.à.r.l. et Cie, S.C.A. (22-24 Boulevard Royal L-2449, Luxembourg; "PayPal"). The data processing serves the purpose of offering you payment via the payment service. By selecting and using payment via PayPal, credit card via PayPal, direct debit via PayPal, the data required for payment processing is transmitted to PayPal in order to enable us to fulfil the contract with you by means of the selected payment method. This processing is carried out on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b GDPR.

For individual payment methods such as credit card via PayPal, direct debit via PayPal, PayPal reserves the right, if necessary, to obtain a credit report on the basis of mathematical-statistical procedures using credit reporting agencies. For this purpose, PayPal transmits the personal data required for credit assessment to a credit agency and uses the obtained information on the statistical probability of a payment default in order to reach a reasonable decision on the establishment, performance or termination of the contractual relationship. The credit report may contain probability values (score values) which are calculated on the basis of scientifically recognised mathematical-statistical methods and include, among other things, address data. Your legitimate interests will be taken into account in accordance with the legal requirements. The data processing serves the purpose of a credit check for contract initiation. The processing is carried out on the basis of art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR due to our overriding legitimate interest in protection against payment default if PayPal pays in advance.

For reasons that arise from your particular situation, you have the right to object to the processing of your personal data carried out on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR at any time by notifying PayPal. The provision of the data is necessary for the conclusion of the contract with the payment method of your choice. Failure to provide such data shall mean that the contract cannot be concluded with the payment method you have selected.

### Use of PayPal Check-Out

We use the PayPal Check-Out payment service of PayPal (Europe) S.à.r.l. et Cie, S.C.A. (22-24 Boulevard Royal L-2449, Luxembourg; "PayPal") on our website. The data processing serves the purpose of being able to offer you payment via the payment service. With the selection and use of payment via PayPal, credit card via PayPal, direct debit via PayPal or "Pay Later" via PayPal, the data required for payment processing is transmitted to PayPal in order to be able to fulfill the contract with you with the selected payment method. This processing is based on Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b DSGVO.

Credit card via PayPal, direct debit via PayPal & "Pay later" via PayPal.

For individual payment methods such as credit card via PayPal, direct debit via PayPal or "Pay later" via PayPal, PayPal reserves the right, if necessary, to obtain credit information on the basis of mathematical-statistical methods using credit agencies. For this purpose, PayPal transmits the personal data required for a credit check to a credit agency and uses the information received about the statistical probability of a payment default for a weighed decision on the establishment, implementation or termination of the contractual relationship. The credit information may include probability values (score values), which are calculated on the basis of scientifically recognized mathematical-statistical methods and in the calculation of which, among other things, address data are included. Your interests worthy of protection are taken into account in accordance with the statutory provisions. The data processing serves the purpose of credit assessment for a contract initiation. The processing is carried out on the basis of Art. 6 (1) lit. f DSGVO for our overriding legitimate interest in protecting against payment default when PayPal makes advance payments.

You have the right to object at any time to this processing of personal data relating to you based on Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO for reasons arising from your particular situation by notifying PayPal. The provision of the data is necessary for the conclusion of the contract with the payment method requested by you. Failure to provide it will result in the contract not being concluded with the payment method you have chosen.

Local third-party providers

When paying via the payment method of a local third-party provider, the data required for payment processing is transmitted to PayPal. This processing takes place on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b DSGVO. For the execution of this payment method, the data may then be forwarded by PayPal to the respective provider. This processing takes place on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b DSGVO. Local third-party providers may be, for example:

* Sofort (SOFORT GmbH, Theresienhöhe 12, 80339 Munich, Germany).
* giropay (Paydirekt GmbH, Stephanstr. 14-16, 60313 Frankfurt am Main, Germany)

Purchase on invoice via PayPal

When paying via the payment method purchase on invoice, the data required to process the payment is first transmitted to PayPal. For the execution of this payment method, the data is then transmitted by PayPal to Ratepay GmbH (Franklinstraße 28-29, 10587 Berlin; "Ratepay") in order to be able to fulfill the contract with you with the selected payment method. This processing is based on Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b DSGVO. Ratepay may conduct a credit check on the basis of mathematical-statistical methods using credit agencies according to the procedure already described above. The data processing serves the purpose of credit assessment for contract initiation. The processing is carried out on the basis of Art. 6 (1) lit. f DSGVO from our overriding legitimate interest in protecting against payment default when Ratepay makes advance payments. For more information on data protection and which credit agencies Ratepay uses, please visit [https://www.ratepay.com/legal-payment-dataprivacy/](https://www.ratepay.com/legal-payment-dataprivacy/) and [https://www.ratepay.com/legal-payment-creditagencies/](https://www.ratepay.com/legal-payment-creditagencies/).

For more information on data processing when using PayPal, please see the associated privacy policy at [https://www.paypal.com/de/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/de/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full).

### Use of the payment service provider Stripe

On our website we use the Stripe payment service of Stripe Payments Europe Ltd, 1 Grand Canal Street Lower, Grand Canal Dock, Dublin, Ireland). The data processing serves the purpose of offering you payment via the payment service. By selecting and using Stripe, the data required for payment processing is transmitted to Stripe in order to be able to fulfil the contract with you with of the selected payment method. This processing is carried out on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b GDPR.

If required, Stripe reserves the right to obtain a credit report on the basis of mathematical-statistical procedures using credit rating agencies. For this purpose, Stripe transmits the personal data required for credit assessment to a credit rating agency and uses the obtained information on the statistical probability of payment default in order to reach a reasonable decision on the establishment, implementation or termination of the contractual relationship. The credit report may contain probability values (score values) which are calculated on the basis of scientifically recognised mathematical-statistical methods and include, among other things, address data. Your legitimate interests will be taken into account in accordance with the legal requirements. The data processing serves the purpose of a credit check for contract initiation. The processing is carried out on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR due to our overriding legitimate interest in protection against payment default if Stripe pays in advance.

For reasons that arise from your particular situation, you have the right to object to the processing of your personal data carried out on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR at any time by notifying Stripe. The provision of the data is necessary for the conclusion of the contract with the payment method of your choice. Failure to provide such data shall mean that the contract cannot be concluded with the payment method you have selected.

All Stripe transactions are subject to Stripe Privacy Policy. You can find these at [https://stripe.com/de/privacy](https://stripe.com/de/privacy).

Cookies
-------

Our website uses cookies. Cookies are small text files which are saved in a user’s internet browser or by the user’s internet browser on their computer system. When a user calls up a website, a cookie may be saved on the user’s operating system. This cookie contains a characteristic character string which allows the browser to be clearly identified when the website is called up again.

Cookies will be stored on your computer. You therefore have full control over the use of cookies. By choosing corresponding technical settings in your internet browser, you can be notified before the setting of cookies and you can decide whether to accept this setting in each individual case as well as prevent the storage of cookies and transmission of the data they contain. Cookies which have already been saved may be deleted at any time. We would, however, like to point out that this may prevent you from making full use of all the functions of this website.

Using the links below, you can find out how to manage cookies (or deactivate them, among other things) in major browsers:

* Chrome Browser: [https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?hl=en](https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?hl=en)
* Microsoft Edge: [https://support.microsoft.com/de-de/microsoft-edge/cookies-in-microsoft-edge-lB6schen-63947406-40ac-c3b8-57b9-2a946a29ae09](https://support.microsoft.com/de-de/microsoft-edge/cookies-in-microsoft-edge-lB6schen-63947406-40ac-c3b8-57b9-2a946a29ae09)
* Mozilla Firefox: [https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)
* Safari: [https://support.apple.com/de-de/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac](https://support.apple.com/de-de/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac)

### Technically necessary cookies

Insofar as no other information is given in the data protection declaration below we use only these technically necessary cookies cookies to make our offering more user-friendly, effective and secure. Cookies also allow our systems to recognise your browser after a page change and to offer you services. Some functions of our website cannot be offered without the use of cookies. These services require the browser to be recognised again after a page change.

The use of cookies or comparable technologies is carried out on the basis of Art. 25 para. 2 TTDSG. Processing is carried out on the basis of art. 6 (1) lit. f GDPR due to our largely justified interest in ensuring the optimal functionality of the website as well as a user-friendly and effective design of our range of services.

**You have the right to veto this processing of your personal data according to art. 6 (1) lit. f GDPR, for reasons relating to your personal situation.**

Plug-ins
--------

### Use of social plug-ins

Our website uses social network plug-ins. The integration of social plug-ins and the data processing associated with this serves the purpose of optimising the advertising for our products.

The integration of social plug-ins involves a connection between your computer and the servers of the service provider of the social network which then instructs your web browser to display the plug-in on that web page, provided you have expressly consented to this. In this process, both your IP address as well as the information on which web pages you have visited will be transmitted to the provider’s servers. This happens regardless of whether you are registered with or logged into the social network. The information is transferred even if users are not registered or logged in. Should you be connected simultaneously with one or more of your social network accounts, the collected information may also be assigned to your corresponding profiles. When using the plug-in functions (e.g. by pressing the appropriate button), this information will also be assigned to your user account. You can therefore prevent this assignment by logging yourself out before visiting our website and before activating the button for your social media accounts.

The use of cookies or comparable technologies is carried out with your consent on the basis of Art. 25 para. 1 p. 1 TTDSG in conjunction with Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR. The processing of your personal data is carried out with your consent on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR. You can withdraw your consent at any time without affecting the legality of the processing carried out with your consent up to the withdrawal.

The following social networks are integrated in our website through social plug-ins. You can find more detailed information on the scope and purpose of collection and use of the data and your associated rights and options for protecting your privacy in the provider’s privacy policy via the link.

Facebook by Meta Platforms Ireland Limited (4 Grand Canal Square, Grand Canal Harbour, Dublin 2, Irland).

Meta Platforms Ireland and we are jointly responsible for the collection of your data and the transfer of this data to Facebook when the service is integrated. The basis for this is an agreement between us and Meta Platforms Ireland on the joint processing of personal data, in which the respective responsibilities are defined. The agreement is available at [https://www.facebook.com/legal/controller\_addendum](https://www.facebook.com/legal/controller_addendum). According to this agreement, we are responsible in particular for the fulfilment of the information obligations in accordance with Art. 13, 14 GDPR, for compliance with the security requirements of Art. 32 GDPR with regard to the correct technical implementation and configuration of the service, and for compliance with the obligations in accordance with Art. 33, 34 GDPR, insofar as a violation of the protection of personal data affects our obligations under the agreement on joint processing. Meta Platforms Ireland is responsible for enabling the rights of the data subject in accordance with articles 15-20 of the GDPR, for complying with the security requirements of article 32 of the GDPR with regard to the security of the service, and for complying with the obligations of articles 33, 34 of the GDPR, insofar as a breach of personal data protection concerns Meta Platforms Ireland's obligations under the joint processing agreement.

Your data may be transmitted to the USA. For the USA, there is an adequacy decision of the EU Commission, the Trans-Atlantic Data Privacy Framework (TADPF). Meta is not certified under the TADPF. The data transfer takes place, among other things, on the basis of standard contractual clauses as appropriate guarantees for the protection of personal data, vavailable at: [https://commission.europa.eu/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/standard-contractual-clauses-scc\_en](https://commission.europa.eu/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/standard-contractual-clauses-scc_en).

For more information on data protection please visit: [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/).

Instagram by Meta Platforms Ireland Limited (4 Grand Canal Square, Dublin 2, Ireland):

Your data may be transmitted to the USA. For the USA, there is an adequacy decision of the EU Commission, the Trans-Atlantic Data Privacy Framework (TADPF). Meta is not certified under the TADPF.The data transfer takes place, among other things, on the basis of standard contractual clauses as suitable guarantees for the protection of personal data, which can be viewed at: [https://commission.europa.eu/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/standard-contractual-clauses-scc\_en](https://commission.europa.eu/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/standard-contractual-clauses-scc_en).

LinkedIn der LinkedIn Corporation (2029 Stierlin Court, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA)

[https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy?trk=uno-reg-guest-home-privacy-policy](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy?trk=uno-reg-guest-home-privacy-policy)

Ihre Daten werden gegebenenfalls in die USA übermittelt. Für die USA ist ein Angemessenheitsbeschluss der EU-Kommission vorhanden, das Trans-Atlantic Data Privacy Framework (TADPF). LinkedIn ist nicht nach dem TADPF zertifiziert.

Twitter de Twitter Inc. (1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, CA 94107, EE. UU.)

Your data may be transmitted to the USA. For the USA, there is an adequacy decision of the EU Commission, the Trans-Atlantic Data Privacy Framework (TADPF). Twitter is not certified under the TADPF.

### Use of Cloudflare

On our website, we use the Content Delivery Network, Cloudflare CDN of Cloudflare Inc. (101 Townsend St, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA; “Cloudflare”). This is a supraregional network of servers in different data centres with which our web server connects and via which certain contents of our website are delivered.

The purpose of the data processing is to optimise the loading times of our website in order to make our offer more user-friendly.

This can involve the collection of, among other things, the following information: IP address, system configuration information, information about the traffic from and to customer websites (server log files).

Your data may be transferred to the USA. For the USA, there is an adequacy decision of the EU Commission, the Trans-Atlantic Data Privacy Framework (TADPF). Cloudflare is not certified under the TADPF. The data transfer takes place, among other things, on the basis of standard contractual clauses as appropriate guarantees for the protection of personal data, which can be viewed at: [https://commission.europa.eu/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/standard-contractual-clauses-scc\_en](https://commission.europa.eu/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/standard-contractual-clauses-scc_en).

Processing is carried out on the basis of Article 6(1)(f) GDPR for the purposes of our legitimate interest in needs-based and targeted design of the website. **On grounds relating to your particular situation, you have the right to object at any time to this processing of your personal data and carried out on the basis of Article 6(1)(f) GDPR.**

For more information about privacy when using Cloudflare, please visit [https://www.cloudflare.com/de-de/privacypolicy/](https://www.cloudflare.com/de-de/privacypolicy/).

### Use of Google Maps

Our website uses the function for embedding Google Maps by Google Ireland Limited (Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland, "Google")

This feature visually represents geographical information and interactive maps. Google also collects, processes and uses data on visitors to the website when they call up pages with embedded Google maps.

Your data may also be transmitted to the USA. For the USA, there is an adequacy decision of the EU Commission, the Trans-Atlantic Data Privacy Framework (TADPF). Google is not certified under the TADPF. The data transfer takes place, among other things, on the basis of standard contractual clauses as suitable guarantees for the protection of personal data, which can be viewed at: [https://policies.google.com/privacy/frameworks](https://policies.google.com/privacy/frameworks).

The use of cookies or comparable technologies is carried out with your consent on the basis of Art. 25 para. 1 p. 1 TTDSG in conjunction with Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR. The processing of your personal data is carried out with your consent on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR. You can withdraw your consent at any time without affecting the legality of the processing carried out with your consent up to the withdrawal.

Further information on the data collected and used by Google, your rights and privacy can be found in Google’s privacy policy at [https://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html](https://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html). You also have the option of changing your settings in the data protection centre, allowing you to administer and protect the data processed by Google.

### Using OpenStreetMap

We use the open-source mapping service of the OpenStreetMap Foundation on our website (St John's Innovation Centre, Cowley Road, Cambridge, CB4 0WS, United Kingdom; "OpenStreetMap"). The data processing serves the purpose of visual representation of geographic information and maps to show you our location.

For this purpose, cookies can be used. Among other things, the following information can be collected and processed: date and time of the call, IP address and information about the browser and the device you are using. This information is assigned to your personal user account if you have an OpenStreetMap user account and are logged in when you visit the website. In this case, the following additional information is collected and processed: User ID, email address assigned to the user account and content blocked by the user. Your data may also be transferred outside the EU to the United Kingdom. The EU Commission has issued an adequacy decision for the United Kingdom.

The use of cookies or comparable technologies is carried out with your consent on the basis of Art. 25 para. 1 p. 1 TTDSG in conjunction with Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR. The processing of your personal data is carried out with your consent on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR. You can withdraw your consent at any time without affecting the legality of the processing carried out with your consent up to the withdrawal. You can find more information on data processing and data protection at [https://wiki.osmfoundation.org/wiki/Privacy\_Policy?tid=331640695983](https://wiki.osmfoundation.org/wiki/Privacy_Policy?tid=331640695983).

### Use of YouTube

Our website uses the function for embedding YouTube videos by Google Ireland Limited (Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland; "YouTube"). YouTube is a company affiliated with Google LLC (1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA; "Google").

This feature shows YouTube videos in an iFrame on the website. The option "advanced privacy mode" is enabled here. This prevents YouTube from storing information on visitors to the website. It is only if you watch a video that information is transmitted to and stored by YouTube. Your data may be transmitted to the USA. For the USA, there is an adequacy decision of the EU Commission, the Trans-Atlantic Data Privacy Framework (TADPF). YouTube is not certified under the TADPF.

The data transfer takes place, among other things, on the basis of standard contractual clauses as suitable guarantees for the protection of personal data, which can be viewed at: [https://policies.google.com/privacy/frameworks](https://policies.google.com/privacy/frameworks).

The use of cookies or comparable technologies is carried out with your consent on the basis of Art. 25 para. 1 p. 1 TTDSG in conjunction with Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR. The processing of your personal data is carried out with your consent on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR. You can withdraw your consent at any time without affecting the legality of the processing carried out with your consent up to the withdrawal.

Further information on the data collected and used by YouTube and Google and your associated rights and options for protecting your privacy can be found in YouTube’s privacy policy ([https://www.youtube.com/t/privacy](https://www.youtube.com/t/privacy)).

Rights of persons affected and storage duration
-----------------------------------------------

### Duration of storage

After contractual processing has been completed, the data is initially stored for the duration of the warranty period, then in accordance with the retention periods prescribed by law, especially tax and commercial law, and then deleted after the period has elapsed, unless you have agreed to further processing and use.

### Rights of the affected person

If the legal requirements are fulfilled, you have the following rights according to art. 15 to 20 GDPR: Right to information, correction, deletion, restriction of processing, data portability. You also have a right of objection against processing based on art. 6 (1) GDPR, and to processing for the purposes of direct marketing, according to art. 21 (1) GDPR.

### Right to complain to the regulatory authority

You have the right to complain to the regulatory authority according to art. 77 GDPR if you believe that your data is not being processed legally.

You can lodge a complaint with, among others, the supervisory authority responsible for us, which you may reach at the following contact details:

Landesbeauftragte für Datenschutz und Informationsfreiheit Nordrhein-Westfalen  
Postfach 20 04 44  
40102 Düsseldorf  
Germany  
Tel.: [+49 211 384240](tel:+49211384240)  
Fax: [+49 211 38424999](tel:+4921138424999)  
Email: [poststelle@ldi.nrw.de](mailto:poststelle@ldi.nrw.de)

### Right to object

If the data processing outlined here is based on our legitimate interests in accordance with Article 6(1)f) GDPR, you have the right for reasons arising from your particular situation to object at any time to the processing of your data with future effect.

If the objection is successful, we will no longer process the personal data, unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds for the processing that outweigh your interests or rights and freedoms, or the processing is intended for the assertion, exercise or defence of legal claims.

### Wanna learn more?  
Get in touch today.

#### Products

#### Products

#### Resources

#### Resources

#### Company

#### Company

#### [](https://gentlent.com/)

Gentlent™ is a software company aiming to make complex web technologies easy and accessible to everyone.[](https://gentlent.com/community)

Gentlent

Copyright © 2019 - 2024 by Gentlent and/or its subsidiaries. All rights reserved. Gentlent® is a registered trademark of Gentlent UG (haftungsbeschränkt) in Germany or other countries. All trademarks, service marks, and company names are the property of their respective owners. Made with ❤ remotely.  

* * *

An official Gentlent website. Official Gentlent websites are always linked from our website [gentlent.com](https://www.gentlent.com/), or contain an extended validated certificate.
